[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Jupiter is growing.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actor played the character of Goldfinger, in the motion picture of the same name?", "correct_answer": "Gert Frobe", "incorrect_answers": ["Cameron Mitchell", "John Agar", "Noel Coward"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Laughter is one of the first expressions of emotions babies learn to convey.  At about what age do babies start to laugh?", "correct_answer": "4 months", "incorrect_answers": ["12 months", "7 months", "18 months"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which planet was named after the ancient Romans\u2019 king of the gods?", "correct_answer": "Jupiter", "incorrect_answers": ["Mars", "Neptune", "Saturn"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In this 2004 remake of the 1978 film of the same name, the opening credits are set to the Johnny Cash song The Man Comes Around.", "correct_answer": "Dawn of the Dead", "incorrect_answers": ["Halloween", "The Hitcher", "The Texas Chainsaw Massacre"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does being obese in some countries with food shortages symbolizes?", "correct_answer": "Wealth", "incorrect_answers": ["Wisdom", "Divinity", "Well-being"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the full name of Charity, the leading character from the popular Broadway musical Sweet Charity?", "correct_answer": "Charity Hope Valentine", "incorrect_answers": ["Charity Mother Hartley", "Charitabella Love Huggings", "Charity Faith Amori"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is black color, or kuro, associated with in Japanese tradition?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Experience", "Age", "Nobility"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What vitamin is the Garden strawberry a rich source of?", "correct_answer": "Vitamin C", "incorrect_answers": ["Vitamin B12", "Vitamin E", "Vitamin K"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What 2002 horror movie is this quote from: Man has only been around for a few blinks of an eye. So if the infection wipes us all out, that is a return to normality.?", "correct_answer": "28 Days Later", "incorrect_answers": ["Zombie Holocaust", "Dawn of the Dead", "FeardotCom"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What differs the Pod People from their human counterparts in the 1956 science fiction movie Invasion of the Body Snatchers?", "correct_answer": "They lack emotions.", "incorrect_answers": ["They dont blink.", "They do not eat.", "They dont sleep."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Pigs are known for their ability to smell what food really well?", "correct_answer": "Truffles", "incorrect_answers": ["Potatoes", "Peanuts", "Carrots"]}]